KATE PRASOLEK

kate.prasolek@gmail.com | 07479929600 | London E1 4RS

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio

linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek

behance.net/kateprasolek

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable graphic designer with a friendly, can-do attitude, experienced in both print and digital design. Self-learner of HTML, CSS and website design with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Crafter with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography, currently exploring motion design field.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop	(4 years)	HTML, CSS	(2 years)	Dotdigital Emails	(2 years)
Adobe inDesign	(4 years)	Adobe XD	(1 year)	Litmus	(2 years)
Adobe Illustrator	(4 years)	Bootstrap	(2 years)	Git / Github	(2 years)
Adobe After Effects	(new)	Google Web Designer	(new)	Wordpress CMS	(5 years)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Graphic Designer at Black Women in Leadership Network, London (Nov 2020 - present)

- Create digital graphical assets for the website, newsletter and social media channels (Twitter, Linkedin).
- Develop coherent brand guidelines and create easy to use templates.
- Create video intros and outros.

Graphic Digital Designer at arteKatie Handmade Cards, London (Jan 2020 - present)

- Establish the brand identity, create a new logo, product photography and photo retouching.
- Produce social media graphics (Instagram, Facebook), banners and promotional marketing collateral.
- Update online marketplace websites, create a blog and social media posts, build landing pages.
- Maintain assets libraries and files organised, keep track of sales and expenses.
 I achieved 50% sales and engagement increase by consistent visuals and social media campaigns.

Freelance Graphic Designer at Naturewatch Foundation, London (May 2020 - Oct 2020)

- Communicate with Campaign Coordinator to create engaging website banners and social media assets.
- Design a printed version of the Compassionate Shopping Guide booklet to the brief and budget. I lowered the printing cost by layout changes and offering a different printing company.
- Website redesign.

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create from brief to completion a wide range of marketing communications such as website banners, emails, gifs, brochures, leaflets, magazine's ads, large format prints and more.
- Work collaboratively with other teams and use feedback to produce final marketing creatives.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.
- Manage multiple digital and print projects simultaneously adhering to meet deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Maintain templates and files, where I implemented a system that sped up the team's work-flow.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Create engaging logos, t-shirts, banners, brochures, leaflets and marketing materials for various clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties and data administration. I put into practice a structured data entry process, that was easier for volunteers to understand and lower the number of mistakes.

Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, sales plans distribution, reporting and customer service. I achieved a 5% increase in sales by visually managing displays throughout the day.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, stock and deliveries, reporting.

INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

Attention to detail	Reliability	Time management	Can-do attitude
Creativity	Professionalism	Organisation skills	Ability to teamwork
Fast-learning	Enthusiasm	Prioritising	Communications skills

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2020	Adobe CC After Effects and XD Experience Design, website /UI design.
2018-19	Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe CC Illustrator.
2017	Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails, HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery.
2016	Graphic Design, Layouts and Composition, Branding and Typography, Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop and inDesign.
2008	Psychology, master degree, Silesian University.